SEÁN KENNELLY

Curriculum Vitae



sean.kennelly@hotmail.co.uk



07908719455



Parsonage House, Woodbury, EX5 1EG

PROFICIENCIES

Skilled in HTML, CSS & Bootstrap

Comprehensive knowledge of JavaScript

Designed, launched and administer two live sites

Excellent problem solver

CORE SKILLS

Organised, professional & flexible

Strong attention to detail

Quick, perceptive and enthusiastic learner

Ability to work to deadlines

Confident and personable with clear verbal and written communication

Comfortable taking on new challenges, motivating others with my enthusiasm and ideas

Adaptable

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I have been living in Australia for four years, and in 2021 took a career break to retrain as a Web Developer. I studied whilst living in Brisbane and returned to the UK at the end of 2022. I am currently continuing my studies online, and am looking to expand my skillset and for my entry into a career in Web Development.

I'm a proven all-rounder with a broad base of knowledge and applicable abilities. I apply the same level of enthusiasm and responsibility to any role and pride myself on my versatility.

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

SEPT 2022 - NOW

I am studying as part of a "Web Developer Bootcamp", in which I am learning advanced JS, Node JS, MongoDB, and React. I am currently building two more sites with plans to launch soon.

STUDENT AT KENT INSTITUTE SYDNEY SEPT 2021 – SEPT 2022

Full time student on a course that covered many diverse aspects of Web and Software Development, including (but not limited to):

- Coding languages (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, PHP, SQL)
- · Real-world projects including websites, databases and hosting
- Development of UI and UX
- Application of SEO
- Client-based approaches to projects

EXETER UNIVERSITY – RESIDENCE ADMINISTRATOR JAN 2018 – OCT 2018

Managing a University residence for students and guests. Responsibilities included:

- Project work: Analysis and presentation of data for department heads. I initiated projects, working closely with my department head to establish them. Once instituted, I independently managed them, delegating my own working hours to their completion. Projects included collection, analysis and presentation of data pertaining to requisite cross-campus maintenance work; department expenditure and takings; and facility requisitions.
- Administration: Managing bookings, allocating rooms, liaising with cleaning staff and other departments, inventory management, audits and departmental banking
- Management of Reception Assistants, including interviewing and hiring, training and supervision
- Customer-Facing: Handling delegate and resident queries, concerns and complaints
- Promoted from role as Residence Support Assistant (July-Dec 2017)

CORE SKILLS CONTINUED

Independent worker with ability to source information

Thorough analytical skills, including application of statistical techniques to interpret and act on data

Strong and developed organisation skills

Consistent output and approach to work

OTHER EXPERIENCE AND EMPLOYMENT

Between 2019 and 2021 I was working and travelling in Australia and New Zealand. The employment I held there was not career focused, so has not been included above under relevant experience.

I worked an assortment of jobs, choosing to focus on variety, location and interest in the position. In many jobs I quickly proved myself responsive, reliable and conscientious, and was promoted or asked to oversee greater responsibility. Most positions were largely independent, so were unsupervised and requiring self-management and effective timekeeping. I sometimes worked in remote and extreme areas, and relished the opportunity to learn from my environment as much as my role. Extreme weather events (floods, cyclones) and the ever-changing face of the Covid pandemic meant that adaptability and a level head were keys to success.

EDUCATION SUMMARY

Establishment - Kent Institute Sydney

Qualification	Date	Grade
Certificate IV in Information Technology (Web Development)	Sept 2022	Pass

Establishment - Plymouth University

Qualification	Date	Grade
Foundation Degree in Arts	June 2012	Pass

Establishment - City College Plymouth, dBs Live Plymouth

Qualification	Subject	Date	Grade
A2 Level	English Literature	June 2009	В
A2 Level	Media Studies	June 2009	В
BTC Level 3	Music Technology	June 2010	Distinction
BTC Level 2	Music Technology	June 2009	Distinction

PERSONAL & VOLUNTARY

In my spare time I am a freelance live sound engineer and have volunteered my efforts at fundraising events. I also make music and have released two albums in the last two years. I am an avid hiker and this year walked 18 miles to raise money for Dartmoor Rescue.